A Finding Aid to the American Federation of Arts Records, 1895-1993 (bulk 1909-1969), in the Archives of American Art AAA.amerfeda
Archives of American Art
Elliot, Lester: 56-2
Elliott, Cecil D.: 58-1
Elliott, James: 58-39
Elliott, Ronnie Rose: 58-26, 58-42
Ellis, Carl: 53-26
Ellis, Clifford: 56-15
Elloian, Peter: 64-7
Elmer, Edwin Romanzo: 62-7, ME-11
Elmer, Jorgen: 64-11
Elmes, Harvey Lonsdale: 61-22
Elvius, Anne-Marie: 53-24
Emanuel, Akiba: 56-2
Emanuel, Bert: 57-16
Embry, Norris: 62-41
Emergy, Lin: ME-56
Emerine, Mary Anne: 53-24
Emerson, Peter Henry: 62-25
Emery, Lin: 55-6, 58-30, 62-40, 65-3
Emiltessile: 61-1
Enders, Cleade: 55-2
Endicott G. & W.: ME-29
Endicott & Co.: ME-29
Engel, Harry: 64-30
Engelund, Svend: 58-15
Enger, Erling: 57-40
Engilberts, Jon: 66-2
Englander, Gertrude: 60-5
Engle, Charlotte: 53-24
Englebrecht: 63-19
Enneking, John J.: 63-1, 64-1
Enos, Robert: 58-35
Ensor, James: 62-27
Eoff & Connor, Garrett & John H.: NY-13
Epler, Rosa Lee: 58-39
Eppelsheimer, Bruce K.: 60-5
Epstein, Jacob: 63-31
Erickson, Eric: 51-15, 55-22
Erickson, Ruth M.: 60-5
Eriksen, Sigured Alf: 57-40
Erikson, D. Erik: 62-10
Erixson, Sven: 62-44
Erkenbrack, Mary: 55-22
Erlanger, Elizabeth N.: 58-3, 64-30, ME-73
Ernest, John: 61-21
Ernest J. Kump & Masten & Hurd: 63-16
Erni, Hans: 53-2, 54-18 58-15
Ernst, James A.: 62-31
Ernst, Jimmy: 51-21, 55-8, 55-9, 55-13, 56-1, 57-9, 58-43, 58-44, 59-1, 65-4, ME-33, ME-42, ME-73, NY-20
Ernst, Max: 55-13, 56-7, 61-9, 62-8, 62-18, 62-29, ME-55
Erwitt, Elliott: 59-56
Escher, Earl: 54-18
Escher, M.C.: 51-3, 56-21
Escher & Weilenmann H.R.: 53-21
Escobosa, Hector: 57-ee
Eshelman, Paul W.: 57-6
Esherick, Joseph: SD-8
Eshkanian, Richard: 57-6, 60-5
Eshkanian, Ruben: 64-23
Eshkanian Ruben & Jack Lenor: 62-15
Eshoo, Robert: 56-12, 56-27
Eskolin, Vuokko: 57-14
Esmonde-White, Eleanor: 56-15, 56-21
Espada, Fernando & Ryder, W. Clayton: 52-7
Espanola, Mercado De Artesania: 61-1
Esteban, Frances: 59-19
Estense, Baldassare: 56-16
Estes, Emily: 58-3
Esteve, Maurice: 60-14, ME-32
Etnier, Stephen: 55-19
Etrange, H.: 56-29
Etter, Russell: 57-14
Etzlaub, Erhard: 55-10
Eugene, Frank: 62-25
Euler, Reeves: 64-30
Evans, Frederick H.: 56-5, NY-1
Evans, Frieda: 58-32
Evans, Helen: 53-17
Evans, James I.: 62-2
Evans, Paul: 57-6
Evans, Walker: 64-28
Everdingen, Allart van: 63-17, MMA-54-3
Evergood, Philip: 55-9, 55-13, 56-1, 56-2, 59-7, 62-1, 62-28, 63-7, 63-33, ME-7, ME-41, ME-73, NY-18
Evett, Kenneth: 53-5
Evjenth, Henry A.: 58-32
Ewing, Edgar: 56-19
Exter: 63-19
Exter, Alexandra: 59-19
Eyerman, J.R.: 58-A&B
Fabbri, Agenore: 55-13, 61-2
Fabri, Ralph: 54-16, ME-7
Fader Lester: 57-6
Fager, Charles J.: 62-10
Faggi, Alfeo: 58-16
Fahlstrom, Oyvind: 62-44
Fairchild Aerial Surveys, Inc.: 64-28
Fairman, Edward: 64-1
Fairman, John: 64-28
Faith-Ell, Age: 62-15
Fakhouri, George: 56-29
Falconer, John M.: 64-1, 64-3
Falconetto: 62-15
Falk, Hans: 61-4
Falkenstein, Claire: 65-11
Falzone, Jr., Joseph A. (MD): 57-ee
Falzoni, Giordano: 55-7
Fantin-Latour, Henri: 63-14
Fantoni, Marcello: 61-1
Farber, Sholam: 55-5, 56-2
Farbman, N.R.: 58-A&B, 59-56
Fardon, R.G.: 54-12
Farkas, Charles: 62-40, ME-56
Farnsworth, Jerry: 64-29, 64-30
Farny, Henry F.: 61-3
Farruggio, Remo: 56-2, 57-10, 64-30
Fasano, Clara: 52-4, 53-20
Fasano, Michelangelo: 58-9
Fassbender, Joseph: 59-36
Fattori, Giovanni: 63-10
Faush, Ruth: 61-1
Faust, Birgitta: 62-15
Fautrier, Jean: 61-11
Favarger, Pierrette: 61-1
Favre, Louis: 54-16, NE-96
Fazzini, Pericles: 55-7, 58-40
Fearing, Kelly: 55-5, 57-23
Feasley, Robert: 57-31
Feeley, Paul: ME-59, ME-75
Fegarotti, Michela: 61-1
Fehr & Granger: ME-19
Feigin, Dorothy Lubell: 55-3, 58-3
Feinberg, Idelle L.: 57-12
Feingersh, Ed: 57-16
Feininger, Andreas: 58-20, 58-A&B, 59-56, 63-8
Feininger, Lyonel: 54-10, 54-25, 55-3, 55-9, 55-15, 55-19, 56-2, 56-7, 57-30, 59-6, 59-36, 60-13, 61-25, 62-28, 62-29, 64-10, ME-23, ME-26, ME-31, ME-32, ME-40, NY-5, NY-7&7b, NY-11
Feininger, T. Lux: 56-2
Feitelson, Lorser: 60-41
Feito, Luis: 61-11
Feke, Robert: 59-24, ME-41
Feldman, Walter: 53-5, 56-2, 56-25, 58-3, 60-3, 65-11
Felton, Frances: 57-6
Fendell, Jonas: 60-3
Fendell, Josh: 55-20
Fenn, Albert: 58-A&B
Fenster, Fred: 62-10, ME-75
Fenton, Roger: 56-5, 62-25, NY-1
Fenton, Sophia & John: 61-17
Ferber, Herbert: 57-37, 58-16
Fereilicher, Jane: 60-14
Ferguson, Kenneth R.: 65-7
Ferguson, Nancy: 64-30
Fernandez-Muro, Antonio: 56-15
Ferneley, John: 55-19
Feron, Louis: 58-16
Ferrant, Angel: 61-11
Ferrara, Jackie: 64-25
Ferrario: 63-19
Ferreira, Thomas: 58-32
Ferren, John: 56-1, 58-43, 59-23, 62-27, 65-11, ME-41
Ferry, Alan: 61-30
Fett, William: 56-2
Feuerlicht, Herbert A.: ME-75
Fiedler, Robert R.: 60-3
Field, Erastus Salisbury: 62-2, ME-11
Field, Frances: 55-2
Field, Ian: 55-20
Fielding, Newton: 62-12
Fiene, Ernest: 56-2, 64-31, ME-73
Fifield, Lew: 58-32
Figino, Ambrogio Giovanni: 62-20
Fike, Phillip: 57-6
Filitcroft, Henry: 61-22
Finch, F.O.: 62-12
Finch, Keith: 58-5, 64-7
Fine, Perle: 54-27, 55-3, 55-20, 57-32, 57-36, 58-26, 62-37, 62-38, 64-29, 64-30
Fini, Leonor: 59-19, 64-4
Fininger: NY-20
Fink, Bert C.: 62-10
Fink, Herbert: 56-27, 58-39
Finkelstein Louis: 56-2
Finkelstein, Maxwell M.: 61-17
Finlayson, Donald Lord: NY-9
Finne, Henrik: 57-40
Fiore, Joseph: 55-20, 60-1, 64-31
Fiore, Nicola: 59-40
Firm, Max Weltz: 61-1
Fisch, Arline M.: 58-32, 62-10, ME-75
Fischer, Hans: 53-2, 54-18, 56-15, 56-21, 57-3
Fischer, Mildred: 60-5
Fischer, Sam: 53-5, 56-19, 57-9
Fischli, H.: 53-21
Fish, C.B.: 55-19
Fisher, Bud: 57-3
Fisher, Davira: 58-3
Fisher, Edward: ME-29
Fisher, Leonard: 55-5
Fisk, Nancy: 55-20
Fitzpatrick, Daniel: 57-3
Fjeldsaa, Kare B.: 57-40
Fjell, Kai: 57-40
Flack, John: 64-23
Flakstad, Nils: 57-40
Flamen or Flamand, Albert: 63-17
Flannagan: 59-54
Flannagan, John: 59-6
Flannery, Vaughn: 55-19
Fleischel, C.: NY-15
Fleischer, Arlyn: 53-17
Fleischmann, Adolf: 60-41
Fleishman, Jay: 64-21
Fletcher, Raymond: 57-23
Flinick, Govaert: 55-24
Flint, William: 62-12
Floch Jenny Eve: 58-32
Floch, Joseph: 55-3, ME-73
Floore, John W.: ME-19
Flora, James: 52-11
Floris, Cornelis: 63-9
Florsheim, Richard A.: 56-15, 58-15, 64-30, ME-73
Flory, Arthur: 54-18, 58-3, 60-3
Floyd, Arthur: 57-14, 58-32
Flueler, Augustine (Sister): 58-35, 61-1
Fogel, Seymour: 57-1, 57-10, 57-23, 61-26
Fohr, Jenny: 56-25
Foley, Matthew: 62-10
Foley, Maurice E.: 58-3
Follett, Jean: 59-12
Fonta, R.: 54-16
Fontana, Girolamo: 58-9
Fontana, Lucio: 58-23, 59-35, 61-23
Fontebasso, Francesco: 55-24, 59-40
Foppiani, Gustavo: 57-27
Forain, Jean Louis: 54-16, 57-37, 62-5
Forakis, Peter: 64-26
Forbes: ME-29
Forbes, Edward: ME-29
Forbes, Elinor: 55-22
Ford, Betty Davenport: 51-15
Ford, Cocke & Smith O'Neil,Bartlett & Harvey: ME-19
Fordyce & Hamby Associates: 59-25, 62-24
Forlivesi, Mirella: 61-1
Forman, Kenneth: 60-3
Fornas, Leander: 60-12
Forner, Raquel: 60-17
Forrest, Norman: 62-15
Forsberg, Jim: 64-30
Forst, Miles: 60-43
Forster, Claire: 56-29
Forsyth, Constance: 62-3
Fortess, Karl: 56-2
Fosburgh, James: 53-14
Foss, Jeremy Bernard: 65-7
Fossati, Domenico: 58-9
Foster, Doris Collins: 57-6
Foster, Francis: 56-2
Foster, Hal: 57-3
Foster, John A.: 57-6
Fourdrinier, P.: ME-29
Fox, Fonaine: 57-3
Fox, Marilyn: 57-14, 58-32
Fox, Norma A.: 57-14, 58-32
Foy, Gray: 53-5, 57-12, 65-11
Fragonard, Jean Honore: 56-16, 62-27, 67-19, ME-29, NY-21
Frances, Esteban: 57-9
Francescini, Marco Antonio: 55-24, 59-40
Francesco, Piero Della: 57-18
Francesconi, Anselmo: 54-16
Francese, Franco: 58-40
Francis, De Scott John Evans: 56-18
Francis, Sam: 56-12, 60-14, 60-22, 61-29, 62-28, 64-2, 64-20, 65-11, ME-73
Franck Frederick: 59-1, 60-12
Franco: 53-36
Francois, Andre: 61-33
Francoise: VA-53-1
Frank, John: 64-30
Frank, Mary: 62-40, 62-41, ME-56
Frankel, Dextra & Charles: 65-3
Frankenthaler, Helen: 57-12, 59-23, 60-9, 61-29, 62-37, 63-15, 64-12, 64-20, 65-1, 65-11, ME-73
Franklin, Albert E.: 53-17
Franklin, Arlene: 58-32
Franklin, Jenny-Lynn: 57-14
Frano, Theodore S.: 53-1
Fransconi, Frederick (Dr.): 55-13
Fransioli, Thomas: 64-31
Franzen, Ulrich: 58-1
Frary, Michael: 55-2, 57-23
Frasce, Gianfranco: 60-20
Frasconi, Antonio: 53-1, 53-5, 53-16, 55-20, 56-1, 56-2, 56-21, 56-24, 56-25, 56-26, 58-3, 60-2, 60-3, 60-22, 61-9, 62-31, 62-45, 63-12, 64-7, ME-7, NY-3
Fraser, Carol: 58-6
Fraser, Hamilton: 59-31
Frazier, John R.: 64-30
Freborg, Stanley: 64-30
Fredenthal, David: 55-13, NY-20
Fredenthal, Miriam: 62-15
Frederick, William N.: 60-5
Freed, David: 60-3
Freed, Ernest: 58-3
Freed, William: 64-30
Freedman, Louise A.: 64-30
Freedman, Martin: 64-30
Freedman, Maurice: 53-5, 64-30
Freeland, William Lee: 57-10
Freeman, Paul: 58-16
Freilicher, Jane: 56-2
Freiman, May: 61-17
Freimark, Robert: 60-3, 62-3
Freisinger, Casper: 64-9
Frelinghuysen, Suzy: 55-3
French, Jared: 60-1, 62-1
French, Ray H.: 53-16, 60-3
Frenzeny, Paul: 64-1
Frere, Theodore: 65-10
Freres, Bisson: NY-1
Freudenberg, Al: 56-2
Freund, Rudolf: 56-24
Freund, Tibor: 63-24
Frew, J. Arnold: 57-6
Fricano, Tom S.: 60-3, 62-3, 64-7
Friebert, Josepth: 58-6
Fried, Theodore: 55-3
Friedensohn, Elias: 57-12, 59-24, 60-43, 61-7
Friedlaender, Johnny: 56-21
Friedman, Jerrold: 55-22
Friedman, Madge: 57-6
Friedman, Martin: 55-3, 56-2
Frink, Elisabeth: 61-2
Frith, Francis: 62-25, NY-1
Fritzius, Harry: 53-26
Fritzsche, Max: 53-15
Frohlich, Max: 61-1
Fromberg, LaVerne: 56-13
Fromboluti, Sideo: 56-2
Fromentin, Eugene: 63-20, 65-10
Frost, Arthur B.: 59-6
Frost, Terry: 58-15, ME-55
Frost, Jr., William P.: 60-5
Froth, Donald E.: 51-15
Frouault: ME-40
Frsconi, Antonio: 56-26, 63-12
Fuchs, Ernst: 54-16
Fuentes: 63-19
Fueter, Daniel Christian: NY-13
Fujihara, Jun: 65-4
Fujihira, Shin: 65-12
Fujisawa, Junji: 65-12
Fujita, Sadamitsu Neil: 53-1, 55-13
Fuller, Buckminster: 59-15
Fuller, George: 58-14
Fuller, Sue: 57-32, 57-36, 58-26, 58-43, 59-6, 61-23, 62-8, 65-4, ME-7
Funk, John: SD-8
Funk, Lissy: 61-1
Fuseli, Henry: 67-19
Fuseli, John Henry: 65-10
Futakuchi, Shioko: 65-12
Fyt, Jan: 55-24, MMA-54-3
Gaberel, Rudolf: 53-21
Gabin, George: 64-4
Gabo, Naum: 59-19
Gadbois, Henri: 57-23
Gadzi, Dimitri: 62-40
Gaetaniello, Vincenzo: 58-40
Gag, Wanda Hazel: ME-7
Gaillardet, Joan: 53-26
Gainsborough, Thomas: 55-24, 57-18, 67-19, MMA-54-2, NY-11
Gaitis, John: 56-29
Gaitonde: 59-13
Galicia, Jose Luis: 54-18, 56-15, 60-15, NE-96
Galliari, Giovanni Antonio: 58-9, 63-19
Galvononi, Natale: 61-1
Gamble, Eugene: ME-19
Gambone, Guido: 61-1
Gammell, R.H. Ives: 64-30
Gandolfi, Gaetano: 67-19
Gannett, Ruth Hrisman: VA-53-1
Ganso, Emil: ME-7
Garber, Daniel: 57-11, 63-3
Garbers, Fred James: 58-39
Garcia, Francisco Tod: 61-4
Garcia, Mario: 58-43
Gardner, Alexander: 56-5
Gargallo, Pablo: 61-24
Garner, Alice: 65-11
Garnett, William A.: 63-8
Garnier, Charles: 61-22
Garrett, Lillian: 57-6
Garzi, Luigi: 62-36
Gaspari: 63-19
Gasser, Henry: 53-8
Gatch, Lee: 54-10, 55-9, 56-2, 57-15, 57-28, 58-16, 59-43, 61-7, 62-28, 64-30, ME-7, ME-41, ME-73
Gates: 63-19
Gates Robert: 55-8, 63-7
Gatje, Robert F.: 63-16
Gaudnek, Walter: ME-75
Gauguin, Paul: 56-15, 57-18, 57-40, 60-14, 62-5, 63-14
Gaw, William A.: 53-5
Gaymer, Dorothy O.: 53-24
Gear, William: 58-15, NE-96
Gechtoff, Sonia: 58-7, 59-12, ME-33, ME-42
Gee, Bing: 58-42
Gehner, Marjorie N.: 60-5
Geiger, Edith: 64-30
Geiger, Rupprecht: 59-36
Gelb, Jan: 56-1, 57-1, 57-32, 57-36, 58-3, 60-3, 60-24
Gelbart, D.: 58-36
Gele, Emile: 53-16, 55-20
Gelinas, Robert: 61-7, 61-35
Gellee or Gelee, Claude: 62-36, 63-17
Geman, William: 54-27
Gendron, Marcelle Ferron Pierre: 59-3
Genevieve, Mere: 54-16
Genthe, Arnold: 64-28
Gentilhatre, Jacques: 61-22
Gentili, Antonio: 59-40
Gentilini, Franco: 58-23, 59-35, 60-15, 61-16
George, David: 64-21
George, Ernest (Sir): 62-12
George, S.: 58-36
George, Thomas: 55-20, 56-25, 56-26, 60-22, 61-15, ME-59, ME-60
George, P. Hall & Son: 64-28
George, Patrice O.P. Sister: ME-75
Georges, Paul: 60-43, NY-18
Georgiadis, Nicholas: 59-19
Gerbier, Balthazar (Sir): 61-22
Geren, Preston N.: ME-19
Gergely, Tibor: VA-53-1
Gerhart, Richard L.: 58-32
Gericault, Theodore: 67-19, NY-9
German, Ali T.: 56-21
German, Alosh: 56-29
German, School: 55-24
Gernhardt, Henry K.: 57-6, 57-14, 58-32, 62-10
Gerome, Jean Leon: 65-10
Gerrits, Ger: NE-96
Gerson, Hans U.: SD-8
Gertner, Claire: 62-10
Getz, Ise: 58-26
Gheyn, Jacob de: 63-9
Ghezzi, Pier Leone: 55-24, 62-20
Ghisi, Diane: 57-37
Ghisi, Giorgio: 63-9
Giacometti, Alberto: 59-5, 62-29, 60-14, 60-15, 60-42, 61-9, 61-24, 62-8, 63-31, 64-2, 64-10, 64-19, ME-65
Giacometti, Bruno: 53-21
Giani, Felice: 58-9, 59-40
Giauque, Elisabet: 61-1
Gibbs, Howard: 56-27, 64-30
Gibbs, James (Sir): 61-22
Gibson, Blaine: 51-15
Gibson, Charles D.: 59-6
Giebrich, Oscar N.: 64-30
Gifford, R. Swain (Robert Swain): 64-3
Gifford, Sanford Robinson: 60-28, 65-10
Giguere, Roland: 59-3
Gikow, Ruth: 57-2, 63-33
Gil David: 64-23
Gil'ad, A.: 58-36
Gilbert, Stephen: 61-21
Gilk, Ernest W.: 51-8
Gilkey, Godon W.: 62-3
Gill, Eric: 54-16
Gill, James: NY-17
Gillam, Bernard: 57-3, 59-6
Gilles, Werner: 56-7, 59-36
Gillet, Roger Edgard: 58-29
Gilliam, Sam: 66-9
Gilmore, William D.: 55-14
Ginstrom, Roy: 57-6, 64-23
Ginzel, Roland: 55-6, 55-20, 56-25, 58-3
Giobbi, Edward: 58-16, 59-10, 61-2, NY-10
Giorgione: 57-18
Giotto: 57-18
Giovane, Palma: 55-24
Girard, Alexander: 53-17, 63-5
Girard, Andre: 53-25, 58-16, 58-35
Girmaldi, Giovanni Francesco: 64-6
Girona, Julio: 56-2, 58-26
Girtin, Thomas: 62-12
Gischia, Leon: NE-96
Gisel, Ernst: 53-21
Gislebertus: 62-23
Glackens, William J.: 55-19, 57-2, 59-6, 60-27, 62-30, 63-1, NY-16, NY-19
Glarner, Fritz: 59-24, 60-27, 60-41, 61-7, 65-11, ME-73
Glasco, Joseph: 62-40, 62-41, 63-31, 64-10, ME-56, NY-10, NY-20
Glassverk, Hadelands: 57-40
Glavani, Joy: 56-29
Gleason, F.: ME-29
Gleb, Jan: 64-30
Gledhill Wall Paper Company: NY-14
Gleizes, Albert: 54-16
Glen, Paulsen & Associates: 65-3
Glick, John Parker: 58-32
Glickman, Maurice: 52-4
Glines, David: 62-3
Glinsky, Vincent: 52-4, 53-20
Glover, Euphemia: ME-75
Glover, John: 62-12
Godbut, Ghislaine: 53-17
Goddard, George W.: 65-11
Godin, Leon: 58-7
Goerg, Edouard: 62-18
Goertz, Augustus: 60-4
Gold, Charles S.: 62-10
Gold, Leah: 58-3
Goldberg, Harold: 55-22
Goldberg, Michael: 57-12, 60-22
Goldberg, Rube: 57-3
Goldberg, Susan B.: 62-10, 62-15
Golden, William: 60-37
Goldenbloome, D.S.: 55-20, 56-25, 58-3
Goldin, Leon: 54-18, 55-20
Goldrich, Hannah: 58-32
Goldring, Milton: 58-12
Goldring, Will: 58-5
Goldsmith, Deborah: 59-18
Goldstein, Milton: 53-2
Goldstone & Dearborn Harmon & Eustis: 59-27
Goldthwaite, Anne: ME-7
Golemon & Rolfe: ME-19
Golobe, Dorothy: 63-24, 64-25
Goltzius, Hendrick: 54-11, 57-37, 63-9, 64-9
Golub, Ina: ME-75
Golub, Leon: 56-2, 60-4, 60-14, ME-73, NY-18
Golubov, Maurice: 53-16, 55-3, 56-2
Gomez De Kanelba, Sita: 65-6
Gompf, Richard C.: 58-32
Gontcharova, Natalia: 59-19
Gonzales-Tornero, Sergio: 62-8
González, Julio: 61-24, 63-31
Gonzalez, Xavier: 53-12, 56-1, 56-27, 64-30, ME-73
Gooden, Stephen: 54-16
Goodman, Marilyn: 58-32
Goodman, Percival: 64-11
Goodman, Sidney: 62-31, 64-25, NY-10
Goodnough, Robert: 57-1, 58-26, 60-9, 60-14, 61-15, 62-6, 63-7, ME-73, ME-74
Goodnow, Frank: 58-3, 60-3
Goodwin Barbara Eckhardt: 56-13
Goodyear, John: 53-26
Gorbaty, Norman: 55-20, 56-25
Gorchov, Ron: 60-12, 64-12
Gordin, Sidney: 57-1, 58-5, 58-43
Gordon, Joseph F.: ME-19
Gorka, Paul: 65-4
Gorky, Arshile: 55-16, 59-6, 59-23, 59-24, ME-23, ME-32, ME-59
Goro, Fritz: 58-A&B
Gorsline, Douglas: 62-31
Goslee, M.E.: 60-5
Goto, Joseph: 56-2
Gottlieb, Adolph: 53-25, 55-9, 56-1, 56-2, 58-16, 58-42, 58-43, 60-27, 62-29, ME-59
Goudie Harland: 53-16, 60-3, 62-3, 64-7
Gould, Chester: 57-3
Goya, Francisco: 55-19, 57-18, 62-18, 62-27, 64-5, 65-10, MMA-7, NY-9, NY-21
Goyen, Jan van: 62-20, MMA-54-3
Gozzoli, Benozzo: 59-40
Grace, Frederick: 59-40
Grae, Ida Dean: 55-22, 57-6
Graham John: 62-1, 2-27
Graham, Walter N.: ME-19
Gramatky, Hardie: 53-8
Gramcke, Elsa: 60-17
Grammar, George: 57-23, 58-44
Granada, Talleres De Arte: 61-1
Granberg, Sue: 58-39
Granlund, Paul: 65-7
Grant, Alistair: 58-15
Grant, Allan: 58-A&B
Grant, Dorothy J.: 58-39
Grant, Copeland & Chervanek: 64-11
Granville, E. Mario: 62-45
Grasset, Eugene-Samuel: 59-40
Grasten, Viola: 53-24
Grau, Enrique: 60-17
Graves, Morris: 52-11, 54-25, 55-9, 58-42, 59-6, 59-24, 60-4, 60-13, 60-27, 62-1, 62-28, 62-29, ME-7, ME-41, NY-5, NY-20
Gray, Cleve: 55-2, 59-1, 61-15, 62-31, 63-7, 65-1, 65-11
Gray, Virginia: 57-14
Grayson, Marvn: 55-5
Graziani, Sante: 58-39
Greacen, Edmund W.: 61-10, 63-15
Greatorex, Eliza: 59-6
Greaves, Derrick: 60-15
Greco, Emilio: 55-7, 57-34, ME-55
Green: 55-19
Green, James: 53-1
Green, Kenneth: 58-32
Green, Wayne: 57-31
Greenbaum, Dorothea: 52-4, 56-2, 57-1
Greenberg, Gloria: 53-16, 53-26
Greenbie, Barrie: 62-14, 64-35
Greene: NY-20
Greene, Balcomb: 54-10, 55-9, 55-19, 56-2, 59-1, 59-10, 60-4, 60-22, 60-33, 60-43, ME-73, ME-74
Greene, Gertrude: 57-30, 60-41
Greene, Stephen: 51-21, 60-1, 61-26, 62-31, 62-37, 65-4
Gregoire, Odette: 61-1
Gregor, Gino: 56-21
Gregoropoulos, John: 55-6
Gregory, Dorothy Lake: 64-30
Gregory, Jules: 59-12, 64-21
Greuze, Jean-Bapiste: 67-19
Grey: ME-49
Griemert, Hubert: 61-1
Grieshaber, H.A.P.: 59-36
Griffin, Georges: 56-2
Griffith, Roberta: 62-10
Grilley, Robert: 57-12
Grillo, John: 56-2, 58-26, 62-41, 64-30
Grilo, Sarah: 60-17
Grippe, Peter: 53-5, 53-16, 56-25, 57-1, 58-3, 60-22, 62-8, ME-7
Grippi, Salvatore: 58-26, 60-1
Gris, Juan: 59-19, 62-5
Groag, Jacqueline: 53-24
Grode, Shearley: 55-6
Groff, June G.: 62-15, 65-11
Groll, Albert Lorey: 63-15, 64-30
Gromaire: 59-5
Gronendyke, Robert Keith: 57-14
Grooms, Red: NY-17
Gropius, Walter: 59-15
Gropper, William: 53-5, 54-16, 56-2, 59-6, 62-31
Gros, A.: 53-21
Groshans, Werner: 53-5, 55-5
Gross, Anthony: 60-15
Gross, Chaim: 53-20, 56-2, 59-6, 62-40, 63-31, ME-56
Gross, Louise: 55-22
Gross, Sidney: 55-3, 59-10, 64-30, ME-73
Grosshardt, Edwin: 53-2
Grosz, George: 54-25, 56-7, 60-13, 60-27, 61-25, 62-1, 62-18, 62-30, ME-31, NY-5
Grotell, Maija: 57-6
Grotenrath, Ruth: 58-3
Groth, John: 55-13, 56-2
Grucza Leo: 63-7
Grumbel, D.: 58-36
Grunbaum, James: 53-14
Grunbaum, Marian H.: 54-27
Grut, Jeanne: 57-14
Guardi, Francesco: 59-40
Guayasamin, Oswaldo: 60-17
Gudiol, Montserrat: 64-17
Guercino: 62-20
Guerin, John: 57-1, 57-12, 57-23
Guermonprez, Trude: 51-15, 55-22, 58-25, 62-15
Guerrero, Jose: 56-26, 58-12, 58-43, 59-1, 59-23, ME-59
Guerreschi, Giuseppe: 60-20
Guerrier Raymond: 56-15, 58-15
Gugel, Vivian F.: 65-11
Guggenheim, Hannelies: 61-17
Guglielmi, Louis: 53-12, 55-13, 57-30, 60-27, 62-1
Guiette, Rene: 61-4
Guigou, Paul: 63-20
Guimard, Hecter: 63-5
Guimard, Hector: 59-40
Gunn, Arthur: 56-2
Gunn, Nancy Reid: 61-35
Gunn, William C.: 55-14
Gur, I.: 58-36
Gurr, Lena: 58-3, 64-30
Gussow Alan: 64-31
Gussow, Roy: 56-12
Gussow, Sue Ferguson: 64-7
Gustafson, Bob: 57-3
Guston, Philip: 55-13, 57-2, 59-23, 63-1, 64-26, ME-59
Gutteter, Lee: 58-32
Guttuso, Renato: 58-23, 58-40, 61-16
Guy, F.: ME-11
Guys, Constantin: 55-24, 59-40
Guzzi, Jr., George D.: 58-3
Gwathmey, Robert: 55-13, 56-2, 56-26, 59-1, 62-31, 63-33, ME-7, ME-32, ME-55, ME-73
Gwilliam, Luke: 56-2, 56-25, 58-3
Haas, Ernst: 59-56
Haass, Terry: 53-16, 56-25
Haberle, John: 59-34
Hack, Robert H.: 53-16
Hackett, Mary: 64-30
Haden, Francis Seymour (Sir): 63-17
Hadzi, Dimitri: 65-11, ME-56
Haerer, Carol: 58-7
Haferung, Paul: 53-15
Hagan, Frederick: NE-96
Hageman, Ruth: 56-2
Hagenauer, Karl: 61-1
Hague, Raoul: 60-2
Hahn, Joseph: 56-2
Hahn, Judith: 64-7
Haida: 59-4
Haines, Richard: 56-19, 57-9
Hajdu, ?tienne: 62-29, 63-31
Halaby, Samia A.: 65-7
Halavi, Yosef: ME-67
Hald, Dagny & Finn: 57-14, 57- 40
Halem, Henry L.: 62-10
Haley, Patience E.: 54-27
Haley, William E.: 53-25
Halicka, Alice: 59-19
Halkin, Theodore: 64-25
Hall, George Henry: 56-18
Hall, George W.: 65-3
Hall, John: ME-29
Halling, Else: 57-40
Hallman, Ted: 58-25, 58-32, 59-12, 60-5, 62-10, 62-15, ME-75
Hallstrom, Staffan: 62-44
Halpert, Samuel: 61-25
Hals, Frans: 57-18, MMA-54-2
Halsall, William F.: 64-29, 64-30
Halsey, Jabez: NY-13
Halsey, William: 53-5
Halsman, Philippe: 58-A&B
Halstead, Martha W.: ME-75
Haly: 53-36
Hamada, Taisuke: 61-4
Hamaguchi, Yozo: 61-4
Hamann-Hartmann, Thyra: 61-1
Hamblett, Theora: ME-75
Hamill, Virginia: 55-22
Hamilton, Edward: NY-21
Hamilton, James: 64-1
Hamilton, Leah Rinne: 58-7
Hamilton, Robert G.: 56-27
Hammarstrom, Olav: 64-11
Hammer, Darrie: 58-3
Hammersley, Frederick: 60-41
Hammond, Natalie Hayes: 58-16
Hampton, Mark G.: 59-12, 62-34
Han, Herman: 64-9
Hands, George: 65-11
Handy, Jr., Arthur E.: 58-32
Hanhart, M & N: ME-29
Hannah, John: 60-3
Hannasch, Monica: 57-6
Hannawell, Richard L.: 58-32, 60-5
Hansen, Dorothy: 55-20
Hansen, James: 57-16
Hansen, Marc: 51-15
Hansen, Sikker: 52-5
Hansson, Berta: 54-18, 56-15
Haraszty, Eszter: 53-17
Harding, Chester: 63-15
Harding, George: 63-3
Harding, John: 51-15
Harding, William Martine: 64-1
Hardman, Ernest: ME-75
Hardy, Gerald: ME-75
Hardy, Thomas: 55-6, 57-15, 58-7, 58-30
Hare, David: 57-1, 57-38, 60-42, 62-40, ME-56
Harel, P.: 58-36
Harkness, John C.: 62-34
Harmon, Eloise: ME-75
Harmon, Lily: 64-29, 64-30
Harmon, Robert: 53-25
Harmon, Pray & Detrich: 62-24
Harnett: 54-25
Harnett, Joan: 58-32
Harnett, William: 55-19, 59-34, 60-13, 62-7, ME-11, ME-31, ME-41
Harpignies, Henri: 63-20
Harriman, George: 57-3
Harriman, Mary: 56-27
Harrington, Phillip: 57-16, 59-56
Harris, Don: 61-35
Harris, Elizabeth: 62-14, 64-35
Harris, Louis: 55-3
Harrison, Wallace: 59-15
Harrison & Abramovitz: 61-31, 62-24, 65-3
Harriton, Abraham: 64-30
Hart, George Overbury (Pop): 64-3, ME-7
Hart, James McDougall: 60-28, NY-4
Hart, William H.: 61-10
Hart, William McDougall: NY-4
Hartgen, Vincent Andrew: 64-31
Hartigan, Grace: 57-10, 58-26, 59-10, 60-9, 60-14, 60-22, 64-2, 64-20, 64-26, ME-33, ME-42, ME-73
Hartl, Leon: 63-1, 65-2
Hartley, Marsden: 54-10, 54-25, 55-15, 55-16, 57-9, 59-6, 59-31, 60-8, 60-13, 60-14, 60-27, 61-25, 62-17, 62-28, 63-14, 64-31, 65-2, ME-7, ME-23, ME-31, ME-40, ME-41
Hartman, Mary Emily: 57-31
Hartman, Robert Leroy: 56-13, 65-11
Hartman, Rosella: 53-1
Hartung, Hans: 54-18, 56-21, 58-15, 60-14, 60-15, 61-4
Hartung, Karl: 56-7, 59-36, 64-14, NE-48
Hartwig, Cleo: 52-4
Harunobu, Suzuki: 58-17, 60-38, NY-12
Harvard, James: 65-11
Harvey, G.: ME-11
Harvey, Robert: 63-7
Harvey, P. Smith & Associates: ME-19
Harwood, Janet: NY-10
Hasegawa, Sabro: 56-15, 58-42
Haseltine, William Stanley: 59-6, 59-40
Hasen, Burt: 59-10
Hasheian, Henry: 65-11
Hassam, Childe: 54-25, 55-19, 57-11, 58-27, 59-6, 60-13, 62-7, 62-17, 62-28, 63-1, 64-3, ME-7, ME-31, ME-55, NY-16
Hassan, Faik: 56-29
Hassan, Shakar: 56-29
Hasuda, Shugoro: 65-12
Hatchett, Duayne H.: 57-31
Hathaway, Rufus: 62-2
Hatofsky, Julian (Jerry): 59-12
Haubold, Ida: 58-3
Hauser, Alonzo: 56-2
Have, Elisabeth: 57-14
Havell, Robert: ME-29, NY-4
Havens, James D.: 56-25
Haviland, Matilda A.: 59-18
Hawker, Maxwell: 52-7, 53-17
Hawking, Clarence: 64-23
Hawkins, Dennis: 60-15
Hawkins, Glenn D.: 57-ee
Haworth, Miriam: 60-3, 62-3
Hawthorne, Charles Webster: 57-11, 61-25, 62-38, 64-29, 64-30
Hawthorne, Marion C.: 64-30
Hayden, Henri: 60-14
Hayes: NY-20
Hayes, David: 62-14, 62-29, 64-35
Hayes, George: 55-19, 62-2
Hays, Dale: 57-14
Hayter, Stanley William: 53-2, 53-5, 56-15, 56-21, 56-26, 57-9, 58-15, 60-15, 60-22, 62-8, 62-18, NY-3
Heade, Martin Johnson: 60-28, 62-17, 64-1, ME-11, ME-55
Headley, Joseph: 59-18
Healy, George: ME-41
Heath, Adrian: 61-4
Heath, Edith: 55-22, 57-6, 64-23
Heath, William: 64-5
Heaton, Glenn: NY-17
Heaton, Maurice: 64-23
Hebald, Milton: 53-20
Hebert, Robert: 64-30
Hebner, E.F.: 62-31
Hecht, Joseph: 63-17
Hecht, Mary: 61-17
Hecht, Zoltan: 56-2
Heckel, Erich: 56-7, 59-36
Hecker, Franz: 62-45
Heckman, Albert W.: 58-15, NE-96
Heckroth, Hein: 59-19
Hedge, Gene: 58-26, 59-12
Heerbrant, Henri: 61-4
Heesen, Willem: 61-1
Hefferton, Phillip C.: 65-11
Hegelheimer, William: 56-27, 64-30
Heidenreich, Carl: 59-10
Heidrick, Madeleine: 61-35
Heil, Joseph H.: 65-11
Heiliger, Bernhard: 64-14, NE-48
Heima, Tatsuhiko: 55-20
Hein, Ray: 57-6
Heino, Vivika & Otto: 57-6
Heintzelman, Arthur William: 53-5, 54-16
Heinz, Charles L.: 64-29, 64-30
Heisig, Mary: 56-2
Heitschmidt & Thompson: 63-16
Helck, Peter: 53-8
Held, Al: 63-7, 63-30, 64-20